德文
Devon!
不...听着 我们不开心 我们很痛苦
No, no, no. Listen, we're not happy. We're miserable.
伯特
Burt!
他们在地下折磨我们
They torture us down there!
德文
Devon!
- 我们都是囚犯 - 伯特
- We're prisoners! - Burt!
她还活着
She's alive!
(健康部)
(宏观数据精检部)
我猜你就是马克S
I suppose you're Mark S.
- 我... - 我是马克W
- I-- - I'm Mark W.
你们是谁
Who are you people?
你愿意换个名字
Would you be open to using a different first name
以避免混淆吗
to avoid confusion?
欢迎回来 马克S
Welcome back, Mark S.
好久不见
Been a minute.
他们去哪了
Where are they?
我觉得 还是等到
I think it's best to save any queries
去了管理层办公室再问问题吧
till we arrive at the management office.
他们被辞退了吗
Were they fired?
你可以把气球放在我旧桌子边的门厅里
You can leave the balloons in the foyer by my old desk.
我们有许多要讨论的事 别让气球分了你的心
We've much to discuss, and I don't want them distracting you.
我保证 不会拿走你的气球的
I assure you, they won't be taken.
米尔奇克先生 拜托了
Mr. Milchick, please.
你们五个月前做的事
What you all did five months ago
是这家公司历史上最痛苦的时刻之一
was one of the most painful moments in the history of this company.
五个月
Five months?
我也因此受到了影响
I, too, was wounded by it.
但不经历痛苦就无法治愈 对吗
But we must be cut to heal, mustn't we?
等等 你刚说你的“旧办公室”
Wait, did you say your old office?
马克 这是黄小姐
Mark, this is Miss Huang.
黄小姐 这是马克S
Miss Huang, Mark S.
你好
Hello.
我们聊的时候 可以请她保管你的气球
She'll be happy to mind your balloons while we chat.
这边 马克
Right this way, Mark.
你可以关上门
You can shut it.
这正常吗 让小孩...
Is it normal for a child to--
房间很乱 你别介意
Excuse the clutter.
好吧 到底是怎么回事
Okay. What's happening?
科贝尔女士已经从公司离职了
Ms. Cobel is no longer with this company.
现在我是分离楼层的主管
I now manage the severed floor.
我的团队呢
What about my team?
我们没有辞退他们
We didn't fire them.
赫莉R和欧文B都成功与外面的人联络上了
Helly R. and Irving B. both successfully made contact with persons on the outside,
和你一样
just as you did.
迪伦G外面的自己在事后得知发生了什么
Dylan G.'s outie learned what happened after the fact.
全世界都知道你们四人了
The four of you have achieved international fame.
你们作为一个团体出名了 成了分离改革的带路人
As a group, you've become known as the face of severance reform.
(“里面的自己”成为吹哨人)
- 分离改... - 马克 坐吧
- Severance ref-- - Have a seat, Mark.
你们叛变之后 我们安装了安全门
Shortly before your mutiny, we installed security doors
保证你们不离开宏观数据精检
to keep you in MDR.
此外 科贝尔女士 还会唱诵基尔圣歌的惩罚版本
This accompanied a punitive rendition of the Kier hymn performed by Ms. Cobel.
你记得吗
Do you recall?
我记得
I do.
我把你锁在房间里 像牲畜一样 马克
I locked you in a room like an animal, Mark.
作为一个未分离的人
As an unsevered man,
我这辈子都会记得这件事
I'll carry that knowledge the rest of my life.
但过去五个月
But for the past five months,
我们一直在自问 像哈蒙妮科贝尔这样的虐待狂
we've been asking how a sadist like Harmony Cobel
怎能在卢蒙的土壤上扎根和生长
could take fertile root in Lumon soil.
这说明我们是哪种公司
And what that says about us.
我们也知道 你在你妹妹家醒来时
We also know Ms. Cobel was at your sister's home
科贝尔女士也在场
when you awoke there.
对 为什么
Yeah. Why was that?
我们认为她对你产生了一种痴迷
We believe she'd developed an erotic fixation on you
计划追求你和你外面的自己
and had plans to pursue both you and your outie
希望你们成为“三人情侣”
in what might be termed "a throuple."
什么
What?
幸好她没有成功
Thankfully, she failed at this.
你还没说我的团队去哪儿了
You still haven't told me where my team is.
我们努力了几周 想要召回他们 马克
We tried for weeks to get them back, Mark.
但他们都不同意
None of them agreed.
我们和他们说会进行改革 但那还是不够
We told them of the reforms, but it wasn't enough.
除了我
Except for me?
你外面的自己坚持要回来
Your outie insisted on returning.
事实上 他求我们立即让他回来
In fact, he begged us to let him back right away.
所以其他人...都拒绝了
So the others, they refused?
是的
Yes.
我想听他们亲口说
Well, I'd like to hear it from them.
这不可能
That's not possible.
好好享受你的气球吧
Enjoy your balloons.
对 我们在你来大约一小时前到的
Yeah. We showed up about an hour before you did.
和原来的宏观数据精检比起来 这里有点狭小
It's a little cramped compared to our old MDR,
但我喜欢绿色的地毯
but I love the green carpet.
我们的地毯是焦糖奶油色 键盘是紫红色的
Ours was a crème br?lée and the keyboards were puce.
是紫色
They were purple.
不对 是紫红色 我知道 因为那颜色令我眩晕
No. They were puce. I know because it makes me nauseous,
我也讨厌甜点
and I hate sweets.
说到甜点 我们多长时间 会见到一次那个“米奇”先生
Speaking of which, how much do we see of that Mr. "Milkshake"?
米尔奇克先生
Milchick.
什么
What?
是米尔奇克 不是米奇 我不知道
It's Milchick, not milkshake. And I don't know.
马尔克 哪里能找到墨水 还有铅笔
Marco, where I can find some ink pencils?
文具柜
Supply closet.
我带你去
I'll show ya.
- 所以你真见到外面的世界了  - 是的
- So, did you really see the outie world? - Yeah.
天空是什么样的
How's the sky?
我不知道
I don't know.
(储存柜)
- 怎么 你没见到  - 我是去了外面一小会儿
- What, you didn't see it? - Well, I went outside for a second,
但被我的妹夫转移了注意力
but I was distracted by my brother-in-law.
真的
Seriously?
因为我们列了一份清单 写着我们最想在外面看到什么
Because we made a list of what we'd most like to see on the outside.
天空显然是第一位
And sky was an easy number one.
完全没有“妹夫”这一项
Brothers-in-law weren't even on the list.
谢谢
Grazie.
你能看出我们来自哪个州吗
Could you tell what state we were in?
因为我们在入职调查中 有三个人都填了怀俄明州
Because three of us put Wyoming on our input survey.
- 你见到了孤丘吗  - 没有
- Did you see any buttes? - No.
天 风是什么感觉
Oh, my God. How's wind?
就像有人朝着你呼气 是吗
Is it just like getting breathed on, kind of?
精检员们 你们好
Hello, Refiners.
你好 黄小姐
Hello, Miss Huang.
噢 不好 是传球游戏
Oh, no. It's the ball game.
我们去厨房吧
Let's head to the kitchenette.
好的 那么
Okay. So,
我叫黄小姐
my name is Miss Huang.
今天是我担任副经理的第一天
It's my first day here as deputy manager.
关于我这个人呢 我的上一份工作是交通指挥员
I guess something about me is that before this, I was a crossing guard.
马克W
Mark W.?
为什么你是个孩子
Why are you a child?
因为我出生的年份吧
Because of when I was born.
好吧 我叫马克W
Right. I'm Mark W.
我是5X分支下的宏观数据精检部员工
I'm from the MDR department of branch 5X,
我曾在那里与格温德琳Y共事
where I worked with Gwendolyn Y.
关于我的一件趣事是 我本以为我们分支关闭后
Kind of a fun fact about me is that I thought I'd be permanently retired
我会永久退休
when my branch shut down.
所以这是个惊喜
So this is a nice surprise.
马克S
Mark S.?
好的
Okay.
我叫马克S
I'm Mark S.
我在这里已经工作了两年左右
And I've been here about two years.
关于我的一件事...
Something about me...
是...
is...
我很幸运 今天交到了四位新朋友
that I am lucky enough to have made four new friends today.
真好 马克
That's nice, Mark.
但我必须提醒你 我是主管
But I have to remind you that I'm a supervisor,
不是朋友
not a friend.
三个新朋友
Three new friends.
好的
Okay.
恭喜两位马克 接下来...
Congratulations to our two Marks. And now...
(卢蒙)
你们的永恒区是什么样的
What's your perpetuity wing like?
- 伊根们会动吗  - 不会
- Do the Eagans move? - No.
这样啊 也许是因为这是旧分支
Probably because it's an older branch.
我们的是机械人偶
Ours were animatronic.
它们甚至跳这种舞
They even did this little choreographed dance.
所以你们的伊根只是站着 好奇怪
So yours just stand there? That's weird.
在我的第一个永恒区 伊根们是扫帚做的
In my first perpetuity wing, the Eagans were brooms.
(卢蒙 赞颂基尔)
扫帚
Brooms?
- 每个伊根的脸都是用盘子做的 - 盘子
- Each with a face made of a plate. - A plate?
我们那时很穷
We were very poor.
你们有心肺复苏假人吗
Did you guys have the CPR dummies?
- 有 - 是用什么做的
- Yeah. - What were those made of?
- 扫帚 - 你们有电梯吗
- Brooms. - Did you have an elevator?
我们有...那个词怎么说来着 绳索
We had-- How do you say a rope.
老天爷啊
Jesus.
我走了 你们怎么样
I'm heading out. You good?
是 我也打算下班了
Yep. Just about to close out.
好的 谢谢
Good. Thank you.
其实我之前的团队是一群混蛋
You know, my old team was a bunch of dirtbags.
我们从没完成过配额 一次都没有
We never hit quota. Not once.
但感觉你很喜欢你过去的团队
But it seems like you really liked yours.
所以 我很遗憾
So, I'm sorry.
晚安 马克
Good night, Mark.
晚安
Good night.
嗨 大家好
Hey, everybody.
“外面的自己
"Dear Outie,
我不知道你能否收到这封信 但我写信是想给你提个醒
I don't know if this will reach you, but I'm writing to alert you
分离层办公室的环境险恶
of the heinous conditions in the severed office
是你把我调过来的
to which you have transferred me.
这个分支的主管是一个没头脑的蠢人 他叫米奇”
The branch is run by a shambolic rube who goes by Milkshake."
天啊
Oh, my God.
“能与其愚蠢程度相比的 只有九大核心原则
"A man whose stupidity is rivaled only by that of the nine core principles.
如果你必须继续让我来这里 请考虑给我绑上炸弹
If you must continue to send me here, please consider strapping a bomb to me,
这样我可以同时炸掉米奇 和基尔伊根的灵魂
so that I may explode both Milkshake and the very spirit of Kier Eagan.
充满愤怒的你公司里的自己 马克W”
Wrathfully, your innie, Mark W."
天啊 这很严重
Oh, my God. That's very serious.
这是在说实话吗
Is it earnest?
你真觉得我是没头脑的蠢人
Do you really think I'm a shambolic rube?
等等 你觉得这字条是我写的
Wait, you think I wrote this note?
你是打算栽赃所有人 还是只针对马克W
Were you going to frame all of us or just Mark W.?
这可真是独占“马克”的好计谋啊
Clever way to secure the name for yourself, I suppose?
- 我不知道你为什么恨这个团队 - 我不恨这个团队
- I don't know why you hate this team. - I don't hate this team.
你甚至都没费心改变自己的笔迹
You didn't even disguise your own handwriting.
其实吧 我都不认识这个团队的人
You know what? I don't even know who this team is.
我说了 我想要我的团队
I told you. I want my team.
到底哪个部分你不理解
Which part of that don't you understand?
马克S 此刻我撤去你的部门主管一职
Mark S., at this time, I revoke your status as Department Chief,
该职务将由你的目标受害人 也就是马克W接任
which will be transferred to your intended victim, Mark W.
我接受
I accept.
你将降职至办公室
You will be relegated to the office
必须定期汇报你的工作进度
and must check in regularly as to your progress.
混蛋 其实你都没有妹夫吧
Do you even have a brother-in-law, asshole?
有什么好笑的
What's funny?
你还不知道我对厨房做了什么 对吧
You don't know what I did to the kitchenette yet, do you?
该死的
Goddamn it.
嘿
Hey!
你不能这么做
You're definitely not supposed to do that.
米尔奇克先生 马克S在你的办公室
Mr. Milchick, I've got Mark S. in your office.
他在用对讲机
He's got the speaker.
喂 有人吗 董事会在吗  我是宏观数据精检部的马克S
Hello? Is anyone there? Is the Board on? It's Mark S. from Macrodata Refinement.
好吧 如果你们在 请听我说
Okay. Well, if you're there, please listen.
我知道你们想要公正地对待 记忆分离的人们
Now, I know that you want to do the right thing for severed people,
- 所以你们必须再让我见我的团队 - 马克
- which is why I need to see my team again. - Mark!
如果像你们说的 我们真的是分离改革的带路人
If we truly are the face of severance reform, as you say,
- 那就应该给他们一个机会 - 马克
- then they deserve a chance. - Mark!
拜托了 他们是我的朋友
Please. They're my friends!
你们不能就这样让他们消失 拜托
You can't just make them disappear! Please!
听着 米尔奇克先生 我找董事会只是因为我不能...
Look, Mr. Milchick, I only went to the Board because I cannot--
董事会不会和公司里的记忆分离人交流
The Board does not converse with innies.
你外面的自己出名了 显然让你公司里的自己昏了头
It is clear your outie's fame has gone to your innie's head.
不 我公司里的自己只是希望同事回来 这样才能一起为基尔效劳
No, my innie just wants his coworkers back so we can serve Kier together.
你要辞退我吗
Are you firing me?
你去吧
On you go.
为什么你们不能让他们回来
Why can't you just bring them back?
再见 马克S
Goodbye, Mark S.
等等
Wait!
- 迪伦 - 马克
- Dylan! - Mark.
- 成功了吗  - 是的
- Did it work? - It worked.
- 其他人呢  - 我不知道
- Where are the others? - I don't know.
米尔奇克...我以为自己不会回来的
Milchick was-- I didn't think I was coming back.
- 其实我已经回来几天了 - 什么
- I've been back a couple days already. - What?
对 他们把团队的人都换了
Yeah. And they had a whole new team.
- 科贝尔找人代替了我们  - 不
- Cobel just replaced us? - No.
科贝尔离职了 现在米尔奇克是老大
Cobel's gone. Milchick's in charge.
行 所以刚才把我按倒 把我 最好的一条皮带割断的人是我们老板
Okay, so the man who just tackled me and cut up my best belt is our boss now?
- 让我死吧 - 等等 他按倒你
- Fuck me. - Wait. He tackled you?
对 非常狠 不过也情有可原 毕竟我先按倒了他
Yeah, bad. Which-- I mean, fair, I tackled the man first,
但我又没割断他的皮带
but I didn't fuck with his belt.
“基尔宽恕背叛他的人”
"Kier pardons his betrayers"?
伯特...
Burt!
哥们 你没事吧
Dude, are you okay?
欧文 发生了什么
Irving, what happened?
搞什么 欧文 哥们 怎么回事  你外面的自己没钱了
The fuck? Irv! Dude, what's wrong? You poor up there?
拜托
Come on.
赫莉
Helly!
天啊 你还好吗
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
我没事 你醒了
I'm okay. Did you wake up?
- 是 太疯狂了 - 我也是
- Yeah, it was crazy. - Same.
天 我好担心你
Oh, my God. I was so worried about you.
- 有多久了  - 五个月 可能更多
- How long has it been? - Five months, maybe more.
其他人呢
Where's everybody else?
走吧
Come on.
他们不见了
They're gone.
欧文
Irving?
他不愿意出来
He won't come out.
- 嘿 欧文 - 我很抱歉 马克
- Hey, Irv? - I'm sorry, Mark.
我需要一点时间 拜托
I just need a moment, please.
好的 你慢慢来
Okay. Take your time.
好吧 这是怎么回事 我们惹麻烦了
Okay, so what is going on? We're not in trouble?
我觉得不是 米尔奇克说 我们的讯息传出去了
I don't think so. I mean, Milchick said our message got out.
他说我们出名了
He said we're famous.
每个人都同等地出名 还是某个人最出名
All of us equally or one of us is, like, the star?
不知道 但他好像想辞退我
I don't know. But then he tried to fire me, I think.
为什么
Why?
因为我对新来的人使坏
Well, because I sort of sabotaged the new people.
- 新来的人  - 所以地上到底发生了什么
- New people? - So, what the fuck happened up there?
听我说 米尔奇克很可能要来了
Well, look, Milchick is probably coming.
很好 他的皮带我还没割 告诉我
Good. I owe him a fucking belt cut. Now tell me.
会不会他们在等我们告诉彼此发生了什么
What if they're waiting for us to tell each other what happened
因为他们并不知道发生了什么
because they don't know what happened?
说不定他们此刻正在听 迪伦
I mean, what if they're listening, Dylan?
等等 监控摄像头呢
Wait, what happened to the security camera?
我...
I--
抱歉 我刚才...
I'm sorry, I was...
就是...
just--
你没事吧
Are you okay?
嗨 大家好 我是黄小姐
Hi, everyone. I'm Miss Huang.
米尔奇克先生在休息室等你们
Mr. Milchick's waiting for you in the break room.
到底搞什么鬼 为什么来了个八岁小孩
What the fuck is going on? Why is she, like, eight?
我不知道
I don't know.
等等 他们找人代替了我们
Wait, so they replaced us?
就几天吧
For a couple days.
代替我的是谁
Who was me?
他们不是专门代替你们的人
They weren't, like, specific counterparts.
而是一些...奇怪的人
They were, I don't know, weird.
好吧 我觉得你不该感到难过
Okay. Well, I don't think you should feel bad at all.
- 感到难过  - 对 终结他们的生涯 去他们的
- Feel bad? - Yeah, for ending their lives. Fuck 'em.
我并不是想要...
Well, I wasn't trying to--
不 哥们 别感到难过
No, dude, I'm saying don't feel bad.
我肯定他们是活该
Like, I'm sure they deserved it.
(休息室)
(卢蒙)
宏观数据精检部 欢迎回来
Macrodata Refinement. Welcome back.
请坐
Please, take a seat.
欧文 如果你不介意的话 请留在后面
Irving, if you wouldn't mind being in back.
(我嬉笑上瘾)
高个子帅哥
Tall glass of water.
看来董事会重新考虑我的要求了
I guess the Board reconsidered my terms.
看来是如此
Guess so.
(勤劳工蜂最欢乐)
你们即将看到的影片 从今天以后将播放给每一位
What you're about to see will be shown to every innie who sets foot
踏入这栋楼的公司里的自己
in this building after today.
希望这能让你们理解卢蒙的感受
I hope it will give you a sense of Lumon's feelings.
(卢蒙在聆听)
嗨 从这个角度 你大概认不出我
Hi. You probably don't recognize me from this angle.
我是卢蒙行政楼 501分支
I'm the Lumon Administrative Building, branch 501.
你正坐在我的里面
And you're sitting in me right now.
我的名字很拗口 或者应该说“很拗门”
The name's a mouthful, or as I say, a "doorful."
所以叫我卢蒙就好了
So you can just call me Lumon.
自从1870年建成以来 我经历了许许多多的变更
I've gone through a lot of changes since my siring here in 1870.
但永远不变的是我对员工们的爱
But one thing I've always had is a love for my workers,
无论是分离还是未分离的员工
both unsevered and severed.
别怪我不谦虚
Not to brag,
但我的地下层是卢蒙所在的206个国家中
but my basement floor is one of the premier severed workspaces
最优等的分离工作环境之一
in the 206 countries from which Lumon operates.
嘿 不准在走廊跑
Hey, no running in my halls!
好痒
That tickles.
但什么才能让一栋建筑真的快乐呢
But what makes a building truly happy?
四位宏观数据精检员工
This question came to light when four MDR workers,
对分离的生活感到不满意
dissatisfied with their severed lives,
于是一起想出一个阴谋 卢蒙历史学家将称其为“宏观数起义”
conspired to mount what Lumon historians will forever call
这个问题因此也有了答案
the Macrodat Uprising.
就在我的鼻子下 上演了一出 充满危险和阴谋的人类戏剧
Under my literal nose unfolded a human drama of danger and intrigue.
正义的愤怒
Righteous anger.
让我们把这里夷为平地吧
Let's burn this place to the ground.
灵感
Inspiration.
我们为什么在对真相一无所知中工作
Why are we down here still working in the dark?
和爱
And love.
这什么鬼
What the shit?
宏观数起义掀起了改革的新风
The Macrodat Uprising yielded bounteous reforms.
包括新的美味小食 比如果皮干 青豆罐头
These include tasty new snacks, like fruit leather, cut beans,
圣诞薄荷和莎莎酱
Christmas mints, and salsa.
什...
Wh--
还没说服你吗
Not sold yet?
(卢蒙走廊通行证)
员工奖励也进行了改革
The incentives were also reformed
现在加入了走廊通行证 咬菠萝游戏
and now range from hall passes to pineapple bobbing...
还有全新的哈哈镜屋
to our brand-new playful mirror room.
其实说来有趣 我一辈子 都坐在这个倒影池旁
You know, it's funny. I've sat by this reflective pool my whole life,
但直到四位宏观数据精检英雄 展现无声的勇气后 我才真正看清自己
yet it took the quiet courage of four MDR heroes to show me who I really am.
他们“一石激起千层浪”
They made quite a splash.
说的真对 水塔 为他们 我要感谢基尔
They sure did, Water Tower. And I thank Kier for them.
为宏观数起义 我要感谢基尔
I thank Kier for the Macrodat Uprising.
我知道我们之间有意见分歧
I know we have our differences...
但希望你们明白 我真正尊重你们每一个人
but I want you to know that I truly respect each and every one of you.
我不想成为你们的狱卒
And I don't wanna be your jailer.
今天结束时 你们每个人 将选择是否继续留在公司
By end of day, each of you will choose whether you want to remain here.
不是你们外面的自己 而是你们自己
Not your outies, but you.
如果你们开始处理文件 那我就会当你们选择留下
If you start work on your file, I'll assume you want to stay.
否则 我会让你们去地上 没有任何恶意
If not, I'll send you to the surface. No ill will.
说不定有一天 我会在餐厅请你们喝一杯呢
Maybe I'll even buy you a drink at a bistro one day.
就像分离楼层的其他部分
Like the rest of the severed floor,
休息室没有摄像头 也没有麦克风
the break room has no cameras or microphones.
我们应该留更多空间给个人隐私
Privacy shouldn't mean packing into a supply closet
而不是把它挤得像罐头沙丁鱼一样
like so many sardines.
我真心希望你们都选择留下 一起享受你们帮助建造的东西
I truly hope you all will choose to stay and enjoy what you've helped build.
新的季度 新的开始
A new quarter. A fresh start.
我们一起努力
For all of us.
刚才都是什么鬼
What the hell was that?
是和我们玩重量级心理战呢
Massive-ass head game is what that was.
所以你们在上面都看到了什么
So what the hell did you guys see up there?
这...
Well...
他说这里没有麦克风
He said there were no microphones in here.
是 他说的大话多了去了 所以你就压低声音说吧
Yeah, he says a lot of shit, so just fucking whisper it.
好的
Okay.
我在我妹妹家里 参加为里肯黑尔举行的派对
So, I was at a party at my sister's house for Ricken Hale.
等等 什么
Wait, what?
你认识里肯黑尔
You know Ricken Hale?
他是我外面自己的妹夫
He's my outie's brother-in-law.
什么
What?
不知为何 我们都认识科贝尔
And for some reason, we both know Cobel.
太疯狂了
That's insane.
对 还有一件事
Yeah. Well, there's something else.
就在我换回来之前 我发现了一张婚礼照片
Just before I switched back, I found a wedding photo.
我猜我外面的自己的妻子几年前去世了
Now, I guess my outie's wife died a few years ago.
噢 天
Oh, shit.
而那似乎就是我决定接受分离的部分原因
Which, apparently, is part of why I decided to get severed.
但是...
Except...
照片中的女人是凯西女士
the woman in the photo was Ms. Casey.
凯西女士是你的妻子
Ms. Casey is your wife?
是我外面的自己的妻子
Is my outie's wife.
但她死了
But she's dead.
不 我知道 但就是她
No, I know, but it was her.
可她在地下啊
Then she's down here.
不 我去了健康部 那里没了
No. I went to Wellness. It's gone.
什么叫没了
What do you mean, gone?
已经没有那个地方了
I mean, it's gone.
天啊 马克 你还好吧
Oh, my God. Mark, are you okay?
是 我不知道
Yeah. Well, I don't know.
你呢 你看到了什么
What about you? What did you see?
我看到了
I saw the inside
一个很无聊的公寓内部
of a really fucking boring apartment.
所以你独自一人住
So, you live by yourself?
对
Yeah.
我在看某个电视节目 关于大自然的 我穿着运动裤和T恤衫
I was watching some nature show on TV, wearing sweatpants and a T-shirt.
哪种T恤衫  上面有乐队或口袋什么的吗
What kind of T-shirt? Did it feature, like, a band or pocket?
类似“救救大猩猩”的那种T恤
It was like a "save the gorillas" shirt.
酷啊
Cool.
应该是吧
I guess.
然后呢
And then what?
然后我出门 看到了一个人 他看起来像个园丁
Then I went outside and found a guy. He looked like a gardener.
我把一切都告诉了他 我觉得他好像不相信
Told him everything. I think he kind of thought it was bullshit.
但是 他说他哥哥是警察
But he said that his brother was a cop
他会把一切都告诉他哥哥
and that he would tell him everything.
不知道 抱歉 我真的努力了
I don't know. Sorry, guys. I really tried.
园丁
A gardener?
对
Yeah.
晚上工作的园丁
A night gardener?
我觉得是的 也许他白天有别的工作
I think so. I mean, maybe he has a different job during the day.
你呢 欧文
What about you, Irv?
你们觉得他是认真的吗
Do you suppose he's serious?
说我们可以离开那话
About letting us leave?
欧文 你看到了什么
Irv, what did you see?
上面的世界不属于我们
It's not our world up there.
这就是我看到的
That's what I saw.
拜托
Come on, man.
你可以告诉我们
You can tell us.
是的 没关系的
Yeah, it's okay.
就算不好也没关系
Even if it's bad.
欧文
Irv.
我只想散散步
I just wanna walk for a bit.
- 我去和他聊 - 不...我们该一起去
- I'll talk to him. - No, no. We should all go.
不 他没事的 好吗
No. He's fine, okay?
我和他说 帮他冷静下来 你们回办公室 需要的话我会找你们
Let me talk him down. You go back to camp. I'll get you if I need you.
- 你确定 你... - 但...
- Are you sure? You-- - But--
嘿 欧文不会有事的 对吧
Hey, Irv's gonna be okay, right?
- 对 - 是
- Yeah. - Yeah.
迪伦会处理的
Dylan's on it.
在今天结束前 我们还有时间
And we have till the end of the day.
是
Yeah.
你们在婚礼照片中看起来快乐吗
Did you guys look happy in the wedding photo?
是的 看着很快乐
Yeah, we did.
其实我从来都不... 凯西女士和我没有对彼此有感觉过
You know, I never, like-- Ms. Casey and I never felt that way.
好吧
Okay.
所以你打算怎么做
So, what are you gonna do?
这...
Well...
我得带她离开这里
I gotta get her out of here.
对吧 如果她是我的妻子...
Right? I mean, if she's my wife...
是 当然了 前提是她仍在这里
Right. Of course. I mean, assuming she's still here.
不过严格说来 她不是你妻子
Though technically, strictly speaking, she's not your wife.
我很肯定戒指是你外面的自己买的
I'm pretty sure your outie bought the ring.
是
Sure.
不过我们算是同一个人
Except, you know, we're the same-ish person.
所以 情况很复杂
So, it's mushy.
情况复杂
It's mushy?
- 是这样吗 复杂 好吧 - 这...对 听我说 赫莉
- Is that what it is? Mushy? Okay. - It's-- Yeah. Listen, Helly--
其实我们不是同一个人
We're not the same, actually.
我们和外面的自己不是一个人
Us and the outies, we're not.
就我个人而言 我觉得 我们不欠他们任何东西
And speaking for myself, I don't think we owe them shit.
但凯西女士是...
But Ms. Casey is--
她是我们的一份子
Well, she's one of us.
所以如果你想帮外面的自己 查清她遇到了什么事...
So, if you wanna help your outie and find out what happened to her...
我愿意帮忙
I'll help.
所以你打算留下来
So you're staying?
我觉得我会的
I think I'm staying.
- 欧文 等等 - 别烦我 迪伦
- Irv. Hold up. - Leave me alone, Dylan.
好...哥们 是不是... 今天结束前 你不能离开这里
Oka-- Dude. Is it-- You can't leave until the end of the day.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
欧文
Irv.
我没有达成目标
I failed at the objective.
什么
What?
我去找伯特了
I went to go find Burt.
好的 你看到他了吗
Okay. Did you see him?
他结婚了 至少是在和某人交往
He's married, or, at least, he's with someone.
我透过窗户看到了他们
I saw them through the window.
该死
Shit.
我应该为他的幸福感到开心
I should be happy he's happy.
对 但是 看起来你不开心 对吧
Yeah. But seems like you're probably not, right?
我上次感到开心还是 宏观数据精检是自己全世界的时候
The last time I was happy was when all I knew was MDR.
那时我擅长自己的工作
When I was good at my job
而不是去努力找幸福
and not trying to be happy.
我打算离开 迪伦
I'm going to leave, Dylan.
这不是离开 所以别用这个词
It is not leaving. So stop fucking calling it that.
- 我知道 你想...我懂... - 你努力一下吧
- I know, you want-- I know-- - Just fucking try.
你是个好朋友 迪伦
You're a good friend, Dylan.
我去伯特家之前在自己的公寓醒来
Before I went to Burt's, I woke up in my apartment.
什么
What?
我站在某种画架前
I was standing in front of some kind of easel.
要命 上面还有画架呢
Fuck. There's easels up there?
对 我外面的自己 正在画一幅走廊的画 黑色的走廊
Yeah. My outie was working on a painting of a hallway. A black hallway.
就像休息室的那个
Like the break room one?
不 不一样 更黑暗
No, it was different. Darker.
尽头有一部电梯和一个往下的箭头
There was an elevator at the end with a downward arrow.
他画了二十多幅这样的画
He painted dozens of them.
要命 为什么
Fuck. Why?
我不知道 我希望你在我离开前知道这点
I don't know. And I wanted you to know before I left.
好 你不是要离开 你...不
Okay. Well, you're not. You-- No.
停下 听我说
Stop it. Listen to me.
我很抱歉外面的伯特 有一个性感老公什么的
Look, I'm sorry that outie Burt has a hot husband or whatever.
但重点不是他 你爱上的是公司里的伯特
But he is not the point. Innie Burt is the guy you fell for,
我知道 因为我鼓励你去追求他
and I know because I encouraged the courtship.
我...
I--
我想要这一切结束
I want it to be over.
好吧 那等你找到黑色走廊或...
Okay. So then after you find the black hallway or--
我想要这种痛苦结束
I want the pain to be over.
如果他离开了 我也离开了...
If he's gone and I'm gone...
别再这么说了
Stop saying that.
那我们会以某种方式在一起
...then somehow, we'll be together.
他不会希望这样的
He wouldn't want that.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
因为我不希望那样
Because I don't want that.
因为我会很难过
Because I would be sad,
我的工作效率会下降
and I would be less productive,
而我很擅长自己在这里做的工作 虽然不知道是什么
and I'm really good at what I do here, whatever it is.
而你是我擅长它的原因之一 所以求求你 别走
And you're part of what makes me good at it. So please, do not go.
迪伦
Dylan.
我是你最爱的公司福利
I'm your favorite perk.
别把那些扯进来
Don't bring them into this.
我的意思是 如果伯特仍在公司
All I'm saying is, if Burt was still here,
他也会让你留下 去查清楚这里到底是什么状况
he would be telling you to stick around and figure out what the fuck this is.
迪伦G
Dylan G.
(分离区临界点 禁区)
米尔奇克先生想见你
Mr. Milchick would like to see you.
是
Right.
(你好 科贝尔女士)
我知道 但他们说现在应该已经修正了
I know, but they said it would be corrected by now.
应该是“米尔奇克先生”
It should be Mr. Milchick.
米尔奇克 先生
M-R-period-space-M-I-L-C-H-I-C-K.
- 我理解... - 米尔奇克先生
- Well, I sympathize... - Mr. Milchick--
但你能确保处理好这个问题吗 是 谢谢
...but could you please see that it's taken care of? Yes. Thank you.
如果有人打来说开机画面的事
If someone calls about my welcome screen,
立即给我转接
I need you to put that call through immediately.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
你想见我
You wanted to see me?
是的
I did.
谢谢你 黄小姐
Thank you, Miss Huang.
你要为皮带的事道歉
You gonna apologize about the belt?
你妻子叫格雷琴
Your wife's name is Gretchen.
什么
What?
她希望你知道
She wanted you to know.
跟我来
Come with me.
另外 我的确要道歉 迪伦 因为我没有用心聆听
And I do apologize, Dylan, for not being a better listener.
没有听到你的需求
For not hearing your needs.
你看
Take a look.
(外面的家庭探访套间)
这些是新装修工程的设计图
These are blueprints for a new renovation,
我选择不告知你的同事
of which I chose not to inform your colleagues.
(人体工学座椅)
它叫外面的家庭探访套间
It's called the Outie Family Visitation Suite.
(回忆墙)
你是说 可以在地下看到我的家人
Are you saying I could see my family here?
按房间的字面意思 是的
If you take the name of the room at face value, I'd say yes.
我的老天爷
Holy fuck.
可不是嘛
The holiest.
很可惜 你们部门的其他人都是单身
Sadly, everyone else in your department is single.
因此 我要请你不将此事告诉别人
As such, I'm asking that you keep this between us...
- 你是... - 只是为了避免嫉恨
- Are you-- - ...only to avoid resentment.
你为朋友们做了那么多 我可不希望他们与你反目
I'd hate for your friends to turn against you after all you've done for them.
你还好吗
You okay?
我没事
I'm okay.
欧文呢
Where's Irv?
在这
Right here.
欧文 你还好吗
Irv. You okay?
我没事
I'm okay.
(达里奥R格里马尔迪)
(冷港完成进度:67%)
(完成进度:68%)